Hello everyone, I hope you you are having
a wonderful December, I certainly have.
I’ve been spending a lot of time with my
family recently, and this week has been focused
on trying to create a lot of wonderful memories.
So, I realized that while I did have some
video projects I was working on nothing was
going to come together as i anticipated.
I realized it was important to let that go,
and take some time to be with my family and
honor that time together.
My sister is here, Liana.
She is one of my favorite people in this world
apart from my brother, who is helping me film
this video.
Anyway, I know this time of year can be tiring
as well as enjoyable and that you find yourself
tired in January.
I am wishing you the best, that you can rest
and recover and embrace the new year as full
of possibilities.
And I thought since I wont have my sister
over here anytime soon, I would have her share
one of her New Years goals.
Liana: what jumps out at me from what you
shared, is I would say to recenter on gratitude
and things to be grateful for.
Not taking for granted basic needs, all the
blessings in our lives, as a family, as individuals,
and how that can let us grow.
I’m taking this opportunity to foster that
gratitude with people I love.
Paola:I would say my New Years resolutions
are quite similar.
I see in the comments in these videos that
are about happiness and how to find happiness,
and that usually happiness is more of a location.
If you just find the right place to live,
the right environment, then you will be happy.
And definitely I understand that, I have lived
in some nasty places and having a clean and
safe home is lovely, having access to nature
is lovely.
But when I think about was has made the most
impact on my joy on a daily basis, it has
been none of that.
It’s not about whether or not I have access
to a trail or whether or not i have a cottage
I can call my own.
None of those have come close to the impact
of recognizing I have a safe environment.
Not only a safe environment as in a shelter,
but having people in your life, and only allowing
people in your life, that make you feel safe.
I came to appreciate that after experiencing
some relationships that didn’t make me feel
safe and some environments where I didn’t
feel safe.
And that is something I really appreciated
after coming to a place i did feel relaxed
and at ease.
And that, knowing that the people around you
care about you and will prioritize your safety
above everything else is something, that not
so many years ago in a not-so-great place,
I would have given anything for and that is
what keeps me going today.
No matter where my life takes me, whether
I need to leave this place or go back to the
city, no matter what I do I am going to be
so grateful I have that.
That is something so special that we often
take for granted.
Yeah, in my very short live I truly believe
happiness isn’t a specific location.
It is something that can be cultivated in
many places and many walks of life as long
as you have your basic needs met, and I know
not everyone has those basic needs met.
It can take so much time, and at times is
can feel so discouraging to try to pursue
and environment that makes you feel your best
and makes you feel safe, and I know that’s
very hard.
So, I’m sending you all my love and I hope
you as well can find some lovely New Years
resolutions that make you excited about all
the possibilities it holds.
Anyway, I guess that’s what my New Years
resolution is as well, yeah, I really like
not to make tactile resolutions.
Every year for a while I would say less ice
cream, and it would fail every time.
Yeah, I’ve given up on a lot of those things.
But yeah, my New Years resolution is just
being grateful for safety.
Fun fact about my sister, she fights.
Liana:I don’t actually fight.
I do martial arts.
Paola: yeah, she does martial arts, she’s
really good.
Liana: yeah, it’s more like I try to beat
people up and I get beat up, because that’s
how I learn.
Paola: She fights, I hike.
Liana: I like that.
Paola:Sending you all my love, thank you so
much for being here, and I will see you next
week.
Liana:Bye!
(Family singing)